{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Wood Trim Painters","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/62489/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62489,"taskName":"Painting or Staining - Trim","taskDescription":"Paint or Stain Wood Trim","xmTaskDescriptor":"Wood Trim Painters","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"paint, painting, stain, trim, molding, mantel, baseboards, wainscoting, wood","textMessagingName":"Trim Painting Proj","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes both interior or exterior. Small projects like baseboards, crown molding, mantels\r\nPainters generally also handle all relevant prep work including washing, scraping, sanding, caulking, patching \u0026 priming. Note separate categories for whole room painting, faux finishes, textured paint, murals, electrostatic painting, refinishing furniture \u0026 popcorn finishes.","rolloverShortDesc":"Small interior or exterior trim projects like baseboards, crown molding, mantels","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Paint or Stain Interior \u0026 Exterior Wood Trim.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated painters in your area.","htmlTitle":"Interior and Exterior Trim Painters \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Wood Trim Painting \u0026 Staining","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":55,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Paint or Stain Wood Trim","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Interior or Exterior Trim Painting or Staining","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Trim Painting \u0026 Staining Project","urlName":"Wood-Trim-Painting","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Interior and Exterior Wood Trim Painters in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"paint, painting, stain, trim, molding, mantel, baseboards, wainscoting, wood","emcCategoryOid":-12054,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":9053,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62489/":{"taskOID":62489,"originalTaskOID":62489,"setID":9053,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5069,"questionDisplayText":"Type of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6001,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain","answerDisplayText":"Stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503194,"questionDisplayText":"What trim do you want painted?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What trim do you want painted?","shortQuestionText":"What trim do you want painted?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1296,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ceiling molding (picture and crown)","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling molding (picture and crown)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2534,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Floor molding (baseboard, base shoe, and base cap)","answerDisplayText":"Floor molding (baseboard, base shoe, and base cap)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7000,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Window sills/trim","answerDisplayText":"Window sills/trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2004,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Door casing","answerDisplayText":"Door casing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6745,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wall molding (paneling, wainscoting, and chair rail)","answerDisplayText":"Wall molding (paneling, wainscoting, and chair rail)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204072,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Garage door frame","answerDisplayText":"Garage door frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5072,"questionDisplayText":"New color","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will the new color be:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lighter than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Lighter than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1829,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Darker than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Darker than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Same or similar to existing color","answerDisplayText":"Same or similar to existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4000,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Multiple colors","answerDisplayText":"Multiple colors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5069,"questionDisplayText":"Type of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6001,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain","answerDisplayText":"Stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6001,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain","answerDisplayText":"Stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503194,"questionDisplayText":"What trim do you want painted?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What trim do you want painted?","shortQuestionText":"What trim do you want painted?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1296,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ceiling molding (picture and crown)","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling molding (picture and crown)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2534,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Floor molding (baseboard, base shoe, and base cap)","answerDisplayText":"Floor molding (baseboard, base shoe, and base cap)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7000,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Window sills/trim","answerDisplayText":"Window sills/trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2004,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Door casing","answerDisplayText":"Door casing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6745,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wall molding (paneling, wainscoting, and chair rail)","answerDisplayText":"Wall molding (paneling, wainscoting, and chair rail)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204072,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Garage door frame","answerDisplayText":"Garage door frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1296,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ceiling molding (picture and crown)","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling molding (picture and crown)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2534,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Floor molding (baseboard, base shoe, and base cap)","answerDisplayText":"Floor molding (baseboard, base shoe, and base cap)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7000,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Window sills/trim","answerDisplayText":"Window sills/trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2004,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Door casing","answerDisplayText":"Door casing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6745,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wall molding (paneling, wainscoting, and chair rail)","answerDisplayText":"Wall molding (paneling, wainscoting, and chair rail)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204072,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Garage door frame","answerDisplayText":"Garage door frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5072,"questionDisplayText":"New color","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will the new color be:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lighter than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Lighter than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1829,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Darker than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Darker than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Same or similar to existing color","answerDisplayText":"Same or similar to existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4000,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Multiple colors","answerDisplayText":"Multiple colors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lighter than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Lighter than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1829,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Darker than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Darker than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Same or similar to existing color","answerDisplayText":"Same or similar to existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4000,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Multiple colors","answerDisplayText":"Multiple colors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}